// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "WHEN YOU GO SOMEWHERE FOR THE DAY, WOULD YOU RATHER..",
    answer: "WHEN YOU GO SOMEWHERE FOR THE DAY, WOULD YOU RATHER",
    options: [
      "A. Plan what you will and when",
      "B. Just Go!"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "IF YOU WERE A TEACHER, WOULD YOU RATHER TEACH..",
    answer: "IF YOU WERE A TEACHER, WOULD YOU RATHER TEACH",
    options: [
      "A. FACTS-BASED COURSES, OR",
      "B. COURSES INVOLVING OPINION OR THEORY?"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: "ARE YOU USUALLY..",
    answer: "ARE YOU USUALLY",
    options: [
      "A. A “GOOD MIXER” WITH GROUPS OF PEOPLE, OR",
      "B. RATHER QUIET AND RESERVED?"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: "DO YOU MORE OFTEN LET..",
    answer: "DO YOU MORE OFTEN LET",
    options: [
      "A. YOUR HEART RULE YOUR HEAD. OR",
      "B. YOUR HEAD RULE YOUR HEART?"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 5,
    question: "IN DOING SOMETHING THAT MANY OTHER PEOPLE DO, WOULD YOU 
RATHER..",
    answer: "IN DOING SOMETHING THAT MANY OTHER PEOPLE DO, WOULD YOU 
RATHER",
    options: [
      "A. INVENT A WAY OF YOUR OWN, OR",
      "B. DO IT IN THE ACCEPTED WAY?"
    ]
  },
   {
    numb: 6,
    question: "AMONG YOUR FRIENDS ARE YOU..",
    answer: "AMONG YOUR FRIENDS ARE YOU",
    options: [
      "A. FULL OF NEWS ABOUT EVERYBODY, OR",
      "B. ONE OF THE LAST TO HEAR WHAT IS GOING ON?"
    ]
  },
   {
    numb: 7,
    question: "DOES THE IDEA OF MAKING A LIST OF WHAT YOU SHOULD GET DONE 
OVER A WEEKEND..",
    answer: "DOES THE IDEA OF MAKING A LIST OF WHAT YOU SHOULD GET DONE 
OVER A WEEKEND",
    options: [
      "A. HELP YOU, OR",
      "B. STRESS YOU, OR",
      "C. POSITIVELY DEPRESS YOU?"
    ]
  },
 {
    numb: 8,
    question: "WHEN YOU HAVE A SPECIAL JOB TO DO, DO YOU LIKE TO..",
    answer: "WHEN YOU HAVE A SPECIAL JOB TO DO, DO YOU LIKE TO",
    options: [
      "A. ORGANIZE IT CAREFULLY BEFORE YOU START, OR",
      "B. FIND OUT WHAT IS NECESSARY AS YOU GO ALONG?"
    ]
  },
{
    numb: 9,
    question: "DO YOU TEND TO HAVE..",
    answer: "DO YOU TEND TO HAVE",
    options: [
      "A. BROAD FRIENDSHIPS WITH MANY DIFFERENT PEOPLE, OR",
      "B. DEEP FRIENDSHIP WITH VERY FEW PEOPLE?"
    ]
  },
{
    numb: 10,
    question: "DO YOU ADMIRE MORE THE PEOPLE WHO ARE..",
    answer: "DO YOU TEND TO HAVE",
    options: [
      "A. NORMAL-ACTING TO NEVER MAKE THEMSELVES THE 
CENTER OF ATTENTION, OR",
      "B. TOO ORIGINAL AND INDIVIDUAL TO CARE WHETHER THEY 
ARE THE CENTER OF ATTENTION OR NOT"
    ]
  },
{
    numb: 11,
    question: "DO YOU PREFER TO..",
    answer: "DO YOU PREFER TO",
    options: [
      "A. ARRANGE PICNICS, PARTIES ETC, WELL IN ADVANCE, OR",
      "B. BE FREE TO DO WHATEVER TO LOOKS LIKE FUN WHEN 
THE TIME COMES?"
    ]
  },
{
    numb: 12,
    question: "DO YOU USUALLY GET ALONG BETTER WITH..",
    answer: "DO YOU USUALLY GET ALONG BETTER WITH",
    options: [
      "A. REALISTIC PEOPLE, OR",
      "B. IMAGINATIVE PEOPLE?"
    ]
  },
{
    numb: 13,
    question: "WHEN YOU ARE WITH THE GROUP OF PEOPLE, WOULD YOU USUALLY 
RATHER..",
    answer: "WHEN YOU ARE WITH THE GROUP OF PEOPLE, WOULD YOU USUALLY 
RATHER",
    options: [
      "A. JOIN IN THE TALK OF THE GROUP OR",
      "B. STAND BACK AND LISTEN FIRST?"
    ]
  },
{
    numb: 14,
    question: "IS IT A HIGHER COMPLIMENT TO BE CALLED..",
    answer: "IS IT A HIGHER COMPLIMENT TO BE CALLED",
    options: [
      "A. A PERSON OF REAL FEELING, OR",
      "B. A CONSISTENTLY REASONABLE PERSON?"
    ]
  },
{
    numb: 15,
    question: "IN READING FOR PLEASURE, DO YOU..",
    answer: "IN READING FOR PLEASURE, DO YOU",
    options: [
      "A. ENJOY ODD OR ORIGINAL WAYS OF SAYING THINGS, OR",
      "B. LIKE WRITERS TO SAY EXACTLY WHAT THEY MEAN?"
    ]
  },
{
    numb: 16,
    question: "DO YOU..",
    answer: "DO YOU",
    options: [
      "A. TALK EASILY TO ALMOST ANYONE FOR AS LONG AS YOU 
HAVE TO, OR",
      "B. FIND A LOT TO SAY ONLY TO CERTAIN PEOPLE OR UNDER 
CERTAIN CONDITIONS?"
    ]
  },
{
    numb: 17,
    question: "DOES FOLLOWING A SCHEDULE..",
    answer: "DOES FOLLOWING A SCHEDULE",
    options: [
      "A. APPEAL TO YOU, OR ",
      "B. CRAMP YOU?"
    ]
  },
{
    numb: 18,
    question: "WHEN IT IS SETTLED WELL IN ADVANCE THAT YOU WILL DO A 
CERTAIN THING AT A CERTAIN TIME,DO YOU FIND IT..",
    answer: "WHEN IT IS SETTLED WELL IN ADVANCE THAT YOU WILL DO A 
CERTAIN THING AT A CERTAIN TIME,DO YOU FIND IT",
    options: [
      "A. NICE TO BE ABLE TO PLAN ACCORDINGLY, OR ",
      "B. A LITTLE UNPLEASANT TO BE TIED DOWN?"
    ]
  },
{
    numb: 19,
    question: "ARE YOU MORE SUCCESSFUL..",
    answer: "ARE YOU MORE SUCCESSFUL",
    options: [
      "A. AT FOLLOWING A CAREFULLY WORKED OUT PLAN, OR ",
      "B. AT DEALING WITH THE UNEXPECTED AND SEEING 
QUICKLY WHAT SHOULD BE DONE?"
    ]
  },
{
    numb: 20,
    question: "WOULD YOU RATHER BE CONSIDERED..",
    answer: "WOULD YOU RATHER BE CONSIDERED",
    options: [
      "A. A PRACTICAL PERSON, OR",
      "B. AN OUT-OF-THE-BOX-THINKING PERSON?"
    ]
  },
{
    numb: 21,
    question: "IN A LARGE GROUP, DO YOU MORE OFTEN..",
    answer: "IN A LARGE GROUP, DO YOU MORE OFTEN",
    options: [
      "A. INTRODUCE OTHERS, OR",
      "B. GET INTRODUCED?"
    ]
  },
{
    numb: 22,
    question: "DO YOU USUALLY..",
    answer: "DO YOU USUALLY",
    options: [
      "A. VALUE EMOTION MORE THAN LOGIC, OR",
      "B. VALUE LOGIC MORE THAN FEELINGS?"
    ]
  },
{
    numb: 23,
    question: "WOULD YOU RATHER HAVE AS A FRIEND..",
    answer: "WOULD YOU RATHER HAVE AS A FRIEND",
    options: [
      "A. SOMEONE WHO IS ALWAYS COMING UP WITH NEW 
IDEAS, OR",
      "B. SOMEONE WHO HAS BOTH FEET ON THE GROUND?"
    ]
  },
{
    numb: 24,
    question: "CAN THE NEW PEOPLE YOU MEET TELL WHAT YOU ARE INTERESTED 
IN..",
    answer: "CAN THE NEW PEOPLE YOU MEET TELL WHAT YOU ARE INTERESTED 
IN",
    options: [
      "A. RIGHT AWAY, ",
      "B. ONLY AFTER THEY REALLY GET TO KNOW YOU?"
    ]
  },
{
    numb: 25,
    question: "(ON THIS QUESTION ONLY, IF TWO ANSWERS ARE TRUE, CIRCLE 
BOTH)
IN YOUR DAILY WORK, DO YOU..",
    answer: "(ON THIS QUESTION ONLY, IF TWO ANSWERS ARE TRUE, CIRCLE 
BOTH)
IN YOUR DAILY WORK, DO YOU",
    options: [
      "A. USUALLY PLAN YOUR WORK SO YOU WON’T NEED TO 
WORK UNDER PRESSURE, OR ",
      "B. RATHER ENJOY AN EMERGENCY THAT MAKES YOU WORK 
AGAINST TIME, OR",
      "c. HATE TO WORK UNDER PRESSURE? "
    ]
  },
{
    numb: 26,
    question: "DO YOU USUALLY..",
    answer: "CDO YOU USUALLY",
    options: [
      "A. SHOW YOUR FEELINGS FREELY, OR ",
      "B. KEEP YOUR FEELINGS TO YOURSELF??"
    ]
  },

  // you can uncomment the below codes and make duplicate as more as you want to add question
  // but remember you need to give the numb value serialize like 1,2,3,5,6,7,8,9.....

  //   {
  //   numb: 6,
  //   question: "Your Question is Here",
  //   answer: "Correct answer of the question is here",
  //   options: [
  //     "Option 1",
  //     "option 2",
  //     "option 3",
  //     "option 4"
  //   ]
  // },
];
